<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">
        <record id="inspection_job_card_mail_template" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Inspection Job Card Mail Template</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="tk_advance_vehicle_repair.model_inspection_job_card"/>
            <field name="subject">Vehicle Inspection Completed - Important Information Inside</field>
            <field name="email_from">{{object.company_id.email}}</field>
            <field name="partner_to">{{ object.customer_id.id }}</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <table style="width: 100%">
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            Dear Customer,
                            <br/>
                            <h4>
                                <strong>
                                    <t t-out="object.customer_id.name"/>
                                </strong>
                            </h4>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <hr/>
                <p>
                    We hope this email finds you well. We are writing to inform you that the vehicle inspection for your
                    <strong>
                        <t t-out="object.vehicle_brand_id.name"/>
                        &#160;-&#160;
                        <t t-out="object.vehicle_model_id.name"/>
                    </strong>
                    has been successfully completed. We appreciate your cooperation throughout the process.
                </p>
                <p>
                    1 Inspection Report: Attached to this email, you will find the comprehensive inspection report
                    detailing the condition of your vehicle. Please review it carefully to understand the results and
                    any recommended actions.
                </p>
                <p>
                    2 Next Steps: Should you wish to proceed with any repairs or maintenance services, our team is here
                    to assist you. Please contact our service department at
                    <strong>
                        <t t-out="object.company_id.phone"/>
                    </strong>
                    or simply reply to this email, and we will be happy to schedule an appointment or provide further
                    guidance.
                </p>
                <p>
                    We take pride in delivering high-quality service and ensuring your vehicle's reliability. Your
                    satisfaction is our top priority, and we appreciate your trust in our expertise.
                </p>
                <p>
                    If you have any questions or need further assistance, please don't hesitate to reach out to us. We
                    are available to help you during our regular business hours.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Once again, thank you for choosing our services. We look forward to serving you in the future.
                </p>
                <br/>
                <h6>
                    Best regards,
                </h6>
                <h5>
                    <strong>
                        <t t-out="object.responsible_id.name"/>
                    </strong>
                </h5>
                <hr/>
                <span>
                    <h6>
                        <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/>
                    </h6>
                    <t t-out="object.company_id.phone"/>
                    <br/>
                    <t t-out="object.company_id.email"/>
                    <br/>
                    <t t-out="object.company_id.website"/>
                </span>
            </field>
            <field name="report_template_ids"
                   eval="[(4, ref('tk_advance_vehicle_repair.action_inspection_job_card_report'))]"/>
            <field name="lang">{{ object.customer_id.lang }}</field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>
